A Guide to the Legislative Petitions of the General Assembly, 1776-1865
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Miscellaneous (Alphabetical), 1748-1875, Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 303-304, 370 (Oversized))
  - Bill to Authorize the Sale or Creation of a Lien on Church Property, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 22)
  - Board of Commissioners - General Rule, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 23)
  - Botetourt County
    - Bullett, Thomas & Hogg, James - Certificates, Depositions, etc., 1813 (Box 303, Folder 24)
    - Citizens Opposed to the Division of the County - Letters, etc., 1833-1834 (Box 303, Folder 25)
    - Huff, Peter & Tuttle, James - Certificates, 1776-1777 (Box 303, Folder 26)
    - Peck, William & Others - Chancery Suit, 1828 Dec. 28 (Box 303, Folder 27)
  - Buckingham County - Meredith, Pleasants W. - Letter of Recommendation, 1833 Jan. 22 (Box 303, Folder 28)
  - Buffington, Thomas - Bill to Erect a Dam (Endorsement only), [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 29)
  - Cabell County - Signatures, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 30)
  - Campbell County - Polls, 1844 (Box 303, Folder 31)
  - Caswell County (N.C.) - Haralson, Paul A. - Certificate, 1825 Dec. 6 (Box 303, Folder 32)
  - Certificate - Revolutionary Service - Unidentified, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 33)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Company (Incomplete), [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 34)
  - Chesterfield County
    - Nopson, John & Scott, Walter - Affidavits, 1774 (Box 303, Folder 35)
    - Poindexter, E. W. (Commissioner of the Revenue)- Report, 1823 (Box 303, Folder 36)
    - Trent, E. W. - Statement of Expenditures, 1815-1816 (Box 303, Folder 37)
  - Chew, John - Withdrawal Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 38)
  - Chichester, D. P. - Withdrawal Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 39)
  - Circuit Court for the District of Columbia, 1813 Jan. 11 (Box 303, Folder 40)
  - Citizens of the Commonwealth - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 41)
  - Citizens of the Counties on the River Appomattox - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 42)
  - Citizens of Southwestern Virginia - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 43)
  - Committee of Courts of Justice
    - Report, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 44)
    - Resolution, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 45)
  - Committee on Military Affairs - Resolution, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 46)
  - Committee of Privileges & Propositions - List of Members, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 47)
  - Committee of Roads - Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 48)
  - Culpeper County
    - Ashby, A. L. - Claim & Resolution, 1847, 1850 (Box 303, Folder 49)
    - Broadus, James M. - Affidavit, 1852 Dec. 20 (Box 303, Folder 50)
  - Currence, Will & Whitman, Matthew - Settlement, 1818 Aug. 29 (Box 303, Folder 51)
  - Devisees of Gen. George Washington, & Others - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 52)
  - Dinwiddie County - Freeholders - Resolutions, 1798 Dec. 8 (Box 303, Folder 53)
  - Dromgoole, Alexander - Withdrawal Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 54)
  - Edwards, Newlett - Withdrawal Receipt, 1827 Feb. 24 (Box 303, Folder 55)
  - Elizabeth City County - Slaves Belonging to Lockey Collier - Valuation Certificate, 1778 Nov. 8 (Box 303, Folder 56)
  - Endorsements (Unidentified), [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 57)
  - Essex County
    - List of Expenses, 1779 Oct. 22 (Box 303, Folder 58)
    - Roane, W. - Warrant, 1785 May 10 (Box 303, Folder 59)
  - Fairfax County
    - Davis, Jesse - Certificates, 1803 (Box 303, Folder 60)
    - Langster, James - Treasury Receipts, Certificates, etc., 1835-1837 (Box 303, Folder 61)
  - Fayette County - Huddleston, John P. - Resolution, 1843 Dec. 22 (Box 303, Folder 62)
  - Fifty-Fourth Regiment of Virginia Militia - Memorial, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 63)
  - Fleming, William - Letter of Recommendation, 1814 Jan. 27 (Box 303, Folder 64)
  - Floyd County - Bill, 1858 Jan. 11 (Box 303, Folder 65)
  - Ford, Lewis - Affidavit, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 66)
  - Fragments (Unidentified), [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 67)
  - Frederick County
    - Barton, Richard W. & Sexton, Joseph - Deposition, 1824 Feb. 4 (Box 303, Folder 68)
    - Sydnor, Richard M. - Court Order, 1837 Feb. 17 (Box 303, Folder 69)
    - Tipping, J. - Letter, 1858 Feb. 25 (Box 303, Folder 70)
  - Fredericksburg (Town)
    - Crump, William & Johnston, Fayette - Letter, 1835 Dec. 19 (Box 303, Folder 71)
    - Gordon, William K. & Harrison, John - Letter, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 72)
    - Hazel River Navigation Company - Resolution, 1852 June 1 (Box 303, Folder 73)
    - Notices (Includes Spotsylvania Co.), 1826 (Box 303, Folder 74)
  - Freeholders & Inhabitants of the Western Counties of the Commonwealth (See Oversized), [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 75)
  - Gardner, Charles; Taylor, Benjamin; & Jones, William - Endorsement, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 76)
  - Giles County - Trent, James - Certificate, Court Order, etc., 1861 (Box 303, Folder 77)
  - Gloucester County - Democratic Party - Resolutions, ca. 1857 (Box 303, Folder 78)
  - Goochland County
    - Bill Imposing Further Restrictions Upon the Independent Banks of the State, 1854 Feb. 19 (Box 303, Folder 79)
    - Cole, William & Others - Deed (Includes Fluvanna & Louisa Co.), 1778 March 19 (Box 303, Folder 80)
  - Goodwin, Thomas (Endorsement only), [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 81)
  - Graham, Margaret R. - Memorial, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 82)
  - Grayson County - Militia Fines, 1861 (Box 303, Folder 83)
  - Greenbrier County - Hanna, Joseph - Accounts, 1821 Dec. 15 (Box 303, Folder 84)
  - Halifax County - Rice, John W. - Affidavits, 1830-1831 (Box 303, Folder 85)
  - Hampshire County
    - Committee of Roads & Internal Navigation - Resolution, 1852 Dec. 22 (Box 303, Folder 86)
    - McGowan, John - Bill, 1858 Jan. 8 (Box 303, Folder 87)
    - Notice & Polls (Includes Hardy Co.), 1851 (Box 303, Folder 88)
    - Parsons, David - Notice, 1802 Oct. 19 (Box 303, Folder 89)
    - Reece, Silas - Resolution, 1861 March 18 (Box 303, Folder 90)
    - Welch, Thomas - Account, 1846 Dec. 29 (Box 303, Folder 91)
  - Hamrick, Benjamin - Withdrawal Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 92)
  - Hannah, Samuel - Treasurer's Receipt, 1783 Jan. 8 (Box 303, Folder 93)
  - Hardy County - Bill to Incorporate the Williamsport & Old Field Turnpike Company, 1858 Jan. 27 (Box 303, Folder 94)
  - Harrison County
    - Brice, B. J. - Letter (Includes Monongalia Co.), 1822 Nov. 20 (Box 303, Folder 95)
    - Howard, Joshua - Certificate, 1821 Dec. 12 (Box 303, Folder 96)
    - Lord, Abner - Depositions, 1799 (Box 303, Folder 97)
    - Poll (Includes Monongalia & Randolph Co.), 1841 April 22 (Box 303, Folder 98)
    - Poll (Includes Marion & Tyler Co.), 1844 (Box 303, Folder 99)
    - Polls (Includes Randolph, Lewis,& Barbour Co.), 1844 (Box 303, Folder 100)
    - Tyson, John - Affidavit, 1816 Dec. 18 (Box 303, Folder 101)
  - Hemmings, Martha C. - Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 102)
  - Henrico County
    - Brown, Elijah - Letter, 1852 Feb. 20 (Box 303, Folder 103)
    - Gregory, John M. - Resolution & Chancery Suit, 1834 Dec. 3 (Box 303, Folder 104)
    - Plat, 1875 Jan. 26 (Surveyed) (Box 303, Folder 105)
    - Ryan, Nathan - Affidavit, 1795 Dec. 5 (Box 303, Folder 106)
    - Sealey, John M. - Affidavit, 1847 Feb. 25 (Box 303, Folder 107)
  - Inhabitants of the Country Bordering on the James River and its Branches - Memorial, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 108)
  - Inhabitants of an Unidentified County Asking for a Bill to Reform the County Courts, [N.D.] (Box 303, Folder 109)
  - Isle of Wight County
    - Ballard, Joseph W. - Accounts, Receipts, etc., 1820 (Box 303, Folder 110)
    - Branch, Benjamin - Bill of Sale for Slave, 1801 Sept. 8 (Box 303, Folder 111)
    - Matthews, Saul - Affidavit & Certificate, 1792 (Box 303, Folder 112)
  - James City County - Inhabitants of Chickahominy - Withdrawal Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - Jefferson County - Lucas, William - Power of Attorney, 1861 July 30 (Box 304, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Scotland - Withdrawal Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 3)
  - Johnston, Thomas N. (Endorsement only), [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Lewellyn - Order for Bill, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, William & Barnes, Richard - Accounts, 1748-1751 (Box 304, Folder 6)
  - Kanawha County
    - Commissioners of Revenue - Letter, 1852 Dec. 11 (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - Proceedings, 1853 Jan. 29 (Box 304, Folder 8)
  - Kentucky Counties (Fayette, Jefferson, & Lincoln Co.) - Resolution, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 9)
  - Lancaster County - Crowder, Rachel & Dountin, Isabel - Certificates, 1786 (Box 304, Folder 10)
  - Legal Representatives of Thomas Walker - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 11)
  - Lewis County - Poll (Includes Harrison & Wood Co.), 1842 (Box 304, Folder 12)
  - List of Names, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 13)
  - Lively, E. H. - Certificate, 1862 Feb. 19 (Box 304, Folder 14)
  - Love, Alex - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 15)
  - Mallory, Capt. Phillip - Certificate, 1811 Nov. 26 (Box 304, Folder 16)
  - Mason County - Notice & Proceedings, 1855 (Box 304, Folder 17)
  - Mathews County - Gayle, Martha - Affidavit, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 18)
  - McCarty, J. C. - Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 19)
  - Merchants & Traders - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 20)
  - Meriwether, W. H. & Others (See Oversized), [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 21)
  - Millers on the Rappahannock River - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 22)
  - Monongalia County - Letters, Polls, etc., 1859-1860 (Box 304, Folder 23)
  - Monroe county - Committee of Propositions & Grievances - Resolution (Includes Greenbrier & Fayette Co.), [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 24)
  - Mosby, Daniel L. - Withdrawal Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 25)
  - Navy Office - Letter to Commissary of Stores, 1780 Sept. 28 (Box 304, Folder 26)
  - Nicholas County - Polls, 1851 (Box 304, Folder 27)
  - Norfolk County
    - Harper, Col. John - Letter & Affidavit, 1833 (Box 304, Folder 28)
    - Levy, 1785 March 9 (Box 304, Folder 29)
    - Whiting, Matthew - Summons & Affidavit, 1805 (Box 304, Folder 30)
  - Odd Fellows of the Male & Female Institute - Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 31)
  - Orange County
    - Committee on Free Negroes - Resolution, 1862 Feb. 17 (Box 304, Folder 32)
    - Proceedings, 1861 Jan. 19 (Box 304, Folder 33)
    - Taylor, William - Certificates, 1791 (Box 304, Folder 34)
  - Pamunkey Indians (Endorsement only), [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 35)
  - Petitioners re. Pay of Legislature - Petition (See Oversized), [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 36)
  - Pittsylvania County - Wilkinson, William - Bill, 1808 Jan. 11 (Box 304, Folder 37)
  - Plat
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 38)
    - [N.D.] (See Oversized) (Box 304, Folder 38a)
  - Plat & Survey, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 38b)
  - Portsmouth (Town) - Statistics, 1835-1836 (Box 304, Folder 39)
  - Powhatan County
    - Ligon, Col. William - Letters of Recommendation, 1833 (Box 304, Folder 40)
    - Proceedings, 1813 Sept. 15 (Box 304, Folder 41)
  - Preston, William - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 42)
  - Prince Edward County - Jones, Charles - Judgment, 1798 (Box 304, Folder 43)
  - Princess Anne County - Warden, James - Affidavit, 1809 Dec. 23 (Box 304, Folder 44)
  - Public Printers (English & Saunders) - Interrogatories, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 45)
  - Randolph County - Currant, William & Whitman, Matthew, 1822 Jan. 1 (Box 304, Folder 46)
  - Rappahannock Manufacturing Company - Memorial (See Oversized), [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 47)
  - Residents of Sundry Counties (See Oversized), [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 48)
  - Resolution, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 49)
  - Richardson, William H.
    - Letter & List of Citizens Commissioned in the Ranger Force, 1863 March 5 (Box 304, Folder 50)
    - Statement, 1843 (Box 304, Folder 51)
  - Richmond City
    - Allen, Philip H. & Virginia A. - Proceedings, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 52)
    - Bulkey, Thomas A. - Court Order, 1864 Feb. 9 (Box 304, Folder 53)
    - Dimmock, Charles - Judgment, 1846 Dec. 30 (Box 304, Folder 54)
    - Gay, E. S. (Capt. of the Public Guard) - Letter & Report of Non-Commissioned Officers & Soldiers (includes residence & age) (See Oversized), 1844 Dec. 16 (Box 304, Folder 55)
    - Hudgins, Emanuel H. - Court Costs, 1831 (Box 304, Folder 56)
    - Penitentiary - Charges, ca. 1861 (Box 304, Folder 57)
    - Shields, John P. - Chancery Suit, Deed, etc., 1839 (Box 304, Folder 58)
    - Taylor, Jaquilin B. - Certificate, 1824 Jan. 2 (Box 304, Folder 59)
    - Tyree, John - Judgment, 1821 Nov. 26 (Box 304, Folder 60)
  - Roanoke County - Bill, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 61)
  - Roanoke Navigation Company - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 62)
  - Rockingham County
    - Certificates, Signatures, & Survey (Includes Shenandoah Co.), 1830 (Box 304, Folder 63)
    - Ragan, Daniel - Certificate, 1822 Jan. 3 (Box 304, Folder 64)
  - Saunders, Nancy - Withdrawal Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 65)
  - Scott County - Kilgore, William - Affidavit, 1850 Dec. 17 (Box 304, Folder 66)
  - Scott, William - Memorial, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 67)
  - Shaffer, C. M. - Letter of Resignation, 1861 Dec. 14 (Box 304, Folder 68)
  - Shelton, Robert - Treasury Receipt, 1783 March 29 (Box 304, Folder 69)
  - Shenandoah County
    - List of Names & Accounts to Defray the Expenses of Public Buildings in the Town of Newmarket, 1792 (Box 304, Folder 70)
    - Smoot, James W. - Act & Resolutions, 1862 Sept. 17 (Box 304, Folder 71)
  - Signatures
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 72)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 73)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 74)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 75)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 76)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 77)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 78)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 79)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 80)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 81)
    - [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 82)
  - Smith, Joseph L. - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 83)
  - Spotsylvania County
    - Affidavits (Includes Fredericksburg), 1826-1827 (Box 304, Folder 84)
    - Briggs, D. - Certificate, 1819 Nov. 24 (Box 304, Folder 85)
    - Hicks, Thomas & Towles, Thomas - Affidavit, 1819 Dec. 6 (Box 304, Folder 86)
    - Holliday, John - Court Documents, Resolution, & Will, 1778, 1818-1819 (Box 304, Folder 87)
    - Proceedings, 1838 Aug. 6 (Box 304, Folder 88)
    - Scrogham, Jacob - Withdrawal Receipt, 1831 Jan. 28 (Box 304, Folder 89)
    - Withdrawal Receipt, 1826 March 6 (Box 304, Folder 90)
  - Stickley, David - Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 91)
  - Subcommittee on the Subject of Enrolling & Organizing the Militia - Motion, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 92)
  - Subscribers - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 93)
  - Subscribers Regiding on the Monongahelia river - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 94)
  - Sundry Officers of the Virginia Line - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 95)
  - Tayloe, John - receipt, 1773 Nov. 30 (Box 304, Folder 96)
  - Triplett, George - Receipt, 1827 Jan. 5 (Box 304, Folder 97)
  - Valentine, Edward - Memorial, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 98)
  - Virginia Marine Insurance Company - Memorial, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 99)
  - Vouchers - Terrell, William; Smith, Arthur; & Mitchell, W., 1777 (Box 304, Folder 100)
  - West, F. M. - Endorsement, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 101)
  - White, George Jr. - Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 102)
  - White, Thomas - Receipt, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 103)
  - Wickham, John - Petition, [N.D.] (Box 304, Folder 104)
  - Williamsburg City
    - Andrews, Robert - Deposition, 1787 Nov. 5 (Box 304, Folder 105)
    - Bowden, S. J., 1843 Dec. 30 (Box 304, Folder 106)
  - Wood County - Spencer, Joseph - Revenue Tax, 1820 Feb. 11 (Box 304, Folder 107)
  - Wynne, F. H. - Letter, 1863 Jan. 13 (Box 304, Folder 108)
- Oversized, Extent: 66 boxes. (Box 305-370)
  - Accomack, Albemarle, Alexandria, & Alleghany County 1786-1862; 1776-1860; 1848-1852; 1852 (Box 305)
  - Amelia & Amherst County 1777-1838; 1778-1788 (Box 306)
  - Amherst County 1790-1798 (Box 307)
  - Amherst & Appomattox County 1804-1836; 1852 (Box 308)
  - Augusta County 1779-[N.D.] (Box 309)
  - Bath & Bedford County 1818-[N.D.]; 1782-1852 (Box 310)
  - Berkeley County 1777-1858 (Box 311)
  - Botetourt County 1777-1797 (Box 312)
  - Botetourt County 1801-1852 (Box 313)
  - Brooke, Brunswick, & Buckingham County 1797-1853; 1778-1782; 1777-[N.D.] (Box 314)
  - Cabell, Campbell, Caroline, Carroll, & Charles City County 1812; 1784-1854; 1777-1832; 1842-1857; 1780-1816 (Box 315)
  - Charlotte & Chesterfield County 1780-1859; 1778-1839 (Box 316)
  - Clarke, Craig, & Culpeper County 1843-1859; 1852; 1777-[N.D.] (Box 317)
  - Cumberland County 1776-1853 (Box 318)
  - Dinwiddie, Doddridge, & Elizabeth City County 1783-[N.D.]; 1847-1856; 1778-1850 (Box 319)
  - Essex & Fairfax County 1791-1835; 1777-1793 (Box 320)
  - Fairfax County 1794-1853 (Box 321)
  - Fauquier & Fayette County 1786-1851; 1832-1833 (Box 322)
  - Fincastle, Floyd, Fluvanna, Franklin, & Frederick County 1776; 1849; 1778-1802; 1803; 1781-1799 (Box 323)
  - Frederick County 1801-1839 (Box 324)
  - Giles, Gilmer, Gloucester, Goochland, & Grayson County 1825-1830; 1855-1860; 1778-1850; 1785-1809; 1841-1848 (Box 325)
  - Greenbrier & Halifax County 1785-[N.D.]; 1776-1809 (Box 326)
  - Halifax, Hampshire, & Hanover County 1818-1842; 1779-1857; 1778-1795 (Box 327)
  - Hanover, Hardy, & Harrison County 1811-1848; 1790-1842; 1787-1845 (Box 328)
  - Henrico & Henry County 1777-[N.D.]; 1779-[N.D.] (Box 329)
  - Isle of Wight, Jackson, James City, & Jefferson County 1791-1815; 1831; 1787-1851; 1811-1854 (Box 330)
  - Kanawha, King & Queen, King George, King William, Lancaster, & Lee County 1800-1854; 1801-1836; 1779-1783; 1786-1812; 1777-1838; 1806 (Box 331)
  - Lewis, Logan, & Loudoun County 1836-1856; 1825-1843; 1782-1799 (Box 332)
  - Loudound, Louisa, Lunenburg, & Madison County 1806-1861; 1805-1819; 1776-1811; 1803-1839 (Box 333)
  - Marion, Mason, Mathews, & Mecklenburg County 1842-1844; 1791-1853; 1814-1849; 1777-1797 (Box 334)
  - Mecklenburg & Monongalia County 1800-[N.D.]; 1781-1832 (Box 335)
  - Monongalia & Monroe County 1836-1850; 1799-[N.D.] (Box 336)
  - Montgomery & Morgan County 1786-[N.D.]; 1825-1833 (Box 337)
  - Nansemond, Nelson, New Kent, Nicholas, & Norfolk County 1785-1844; 1809-1851; 1794; 1850; 1780-1790 (Box 338)
  - Norfolk, Northampton, & Northumberland County 1793-1838; 1818-1852; 1777-1808 (Box 339)
  - Nottoway & Ohio County 1790-1803; 1787-1835 (Box 340)
  - Ohio & Orange County 1835-[N.D.]; 1777-1837 (Box 341)
  - Patrick, Pendleton, & Pittsylvania County 1811-[N.D.]; 1813-1848; 1776-1850 (Box 342)
  - Pleasants, Pocahontas, Powhatan, Preston, & Prince Edward County 1856; 1850-1851; 1788-1833; 1821-1849; 1796-1840 (Box 343)
  - Prince George, Princess Anne, & Prince William County 1792-1848; 1783-1816; 1779-1804 (Box 344)
  - Prince William, Putnam, & Randolph County 1805-[N.D.]; 1851; 1801-1846 (Box 345)
  - Ritchie, Roane, Roanoke, Rockbridge, & Rockingham County 1844-1856; 1855; 1847-1848; 1781-1851; 1799-1846 (Box 346)
  - Russell, Scott, & Shenandoah County 1792-[N.D.]; 1835; 1786-1810 (Box 347)
  - Shenandoah, Smyth, & Southampton County 1816-[N.D.]; 1836-1837; 1787-[N.D.] (Box 348)
  - Spotsylvania County 1777-1850 (Box 349)
  - Stafford, Surry, Sussex, & Taylor County 1779-1838; 1787-[N.D.]; 1777-1850; 1845-1856 (Box 350)
  - Tazewell, Tyler, Upshur, Warwick, & Washington County 1852-1860; 1844; 1855; 1796-1839; 1777-[N.D.] (Box 351)
  - Westmoreland & Wood County 1779-[N.D.]; 1799-1855 (Box 352)
  - Wythe, Yohogania, & York County 1792-1847; 1782; 1784 (Box 353)
  - Alexandria (Town) 1778-1795 (Box 354)
  - Alexandria (Town) & Fredericksburg (Town) 1797-1792; 1778-1834 (Box 355)
  - Fredericksburg(Town) & Lynchburg (Town) 1797-1834; 1792-1806 (Box 356)
  - Lynchburg (Town) & Norfolk (Borough) 1810-[N.D.]; 1776-1789 (Box 357)
  - Norfolk (Borough) 1790-1810 (Box 358)
  - Norfolk (Borough) & Petersburg (Town) 1815-1858; 1779-1792 (Box 359)
  - Petersburg (Town) 1796-1818 (Box 360)
  - Petersburg (Town) 1819-[N.D.] (Box 361)
  - Portsmouth (Town) & Richmond (City) 1834-1847; 1782-1803 (Box 362)
  - Richmond (City) 1804-1817 (Box 363)
  - Richmond (City) 1819-1836 (Box 364)
  - Richmond (City), Williamsburg (City), & Winchester (Town) 1840-[N.D.]; 1777-1806; 1791-1839 (Box 365)
  - Kentucky Counties & Miscellaneous (Chonological) 1779-1790; 1776-1783 (Box 366)
  - Miscellaneous (Chonological) 1784-1793 (Box 367)
  - Miscellaneous (Chonological) 1821-1861 (Box 368)
  - Miscellaneous (Alphabetical) (Box 367)